Evgenii Bykov

Full stack software developer (PHP)

Sillamae, Estonia +372 5808-4707 Archangelsk, Russia +7 (953) 939-30-10

evbkv@outlook.com github.com/evbkv



As an experienced web developer, I possess a broad range of skills in developing websites, from landing pages to BPMS and CMS. I am proficient in utilizing programming languages such as PHP, JavaScript, Python, Java, SQL, MariaDB, MS SQL, JSON, HTML5/CSS3, JQuery, AngularJS, Laravel, React, and Bootstrap. I also have experience in utilizing various tools such as, git/github, npm, Keras, and OpenCV as well as in developing WordPress and WooCommerce websites and PWA. Additionally, I am a professional user of Windows, Linux, and MacOSX operating systems, and proficient in using software applications such as 3dsmax, Corona Renderer, Photoshop, CoralDraw, AutoCad, Figma, and Canva. Moreover, I have Autodesk Certifications to showcase my proficiency in the field.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full stack software developer (freelance)

Projects: PHP, JavaScript, MariaDB, HTML5/CSS3, Bootstrap, Laravel, WordPress. 2022 – now

3D graphic artist (evbkv.ru/3d)

I am a professional archviz CGI. 3dsmax + Corona Render + Photoshop. 2018 – now

Entrepreneur (mropt.com)

I am an entrepreneur with expertise in developing business concepts, handling financial and legal matters, and creating BPMS, CMS, and websites.

2002 - now

Interior Designer (evbkv.ru/design)

I design private and public interiors, sell materials and furniture, organize construction work.

2000 - now

Head of the organization

I worked development of the concept of tourism development in the region, interaction with authorities and business, organization of public events.

2011 - 2017

EDUCATION

Ida-Virumaa Kutsehariduskeskus (Estonia, Vocational education)

Software Developer

2021 - 2023

Autodesk certificates

- Exterior visualization in 3ds max and Corona Render,
- Modeling in 3ds max,
- Intensive interior visualization in 3ds max and Corona Render

2019 - 2020

Northern (Arctic) Federal University (Russian Federation, Higher education)

Civil engineering

1998 - 2003

Secondary School №14 (Russian Federation, Secondary education)

1988 - 1998

HARD SKILLS

Middle

PHP, JavaScript, SQL, MariaDB, JSON, Ajax, HTML5/CSS3, JQuery, AngularJS, Bootstrap, WordPress.

3dsmax, Corona Renderer, Photoshop, CoralDraw, AutoCad, Figma, Canva.

Junior

Laravel, React, Java, Python, Keras, OpenCV, C#, ASP.NET, MS SQL, PWA.

SOFT SKILLS

Creative, Detail-oriented, Teamwork, Time Management, Multitasking, Problem-solving.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English – B1 (spoken less) Russian – native

DRIVING SKILLS

B (1999)

ORGANISATIONS AND AFFILIATIONS

Rural tourism specialist

Government of the Arkhangelsk Region (Russia)

2012 - 2017

DESIRED POSITION

Information Technology

Webmaster, it-specialist, programmer, developer, full stack developer, frontend developer, backend developer, PHP developer, web developer, software developer, computer graphic designer, archviz artist, 3d artist.

Work Type

Employee, contract worker, temporary.

Working Time

Full-time, part-time, freelance.

Locations

USA, Canada, GB, Finland, Estonia or other.

ADDITIONAL INFO

I am married and have two children. My hobbies are history and travels, sports (cycle, fitness, kayak), classic and art house music and movies, old computers. I have a dog, before had a cat and a horse. Lived for 5 years in the village, the hero of the movie with +1M views on YouTube.